### **OBJECTIVE**

As a veteran and junior developer, I want to bring my dedication and myriad of skills to your projects. With a vast amount of experience in multiple industries, I am more than capable of taking on any challenge with determination and success.

## CONTACT

- myronlucan@gmail.com
- Dallas, TX 75230

### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Development Certification Southern Methodist University (SMU) Dallas, TX – June 2024

Bachelors of Business Administration American Military University (AMU), Charles Town, WV - October 2019

## **SKILLS**

- UI/UX design
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- React
- SQL
- Database Management
- Troubleshooting/Debugging
- MERN Stack Development

## **Soft Skills**

- Troubleshooting
- Time-management
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Adaptability

# Myron Lucan

# **FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

# **EXPERIENCE**

## SYSTEM SPECIALIST CLIMATEC LLC.

Apr 2022 - Mar 2024

Demonstrated superior technical and diagnostic skills utilizing Alerton and Distech building management systems (BMS). Managed multiple construction projects within the North Texas region valued over \$1M. Assisted in the design of user applications to monitor building HVAC and diagnostic data for local companies and schools in 10+ North Texas cities.

# CATASTSROPHE FIELD PROPERTY ADJUST ALLSTATE INS.

Apr 2021 – Apr 2022

Constructed loss stories utilizing evidence such as photos, documentation, and correspondence to establish cause of loss and coverage. Delivered accurate coverage decisions to insureds, both in the field and virtually, using policy guidance and precise estimating standards. Drafted estimates using Xactimate software, assessing damages for both CAT and normal claims, maintaining a claim accuracy of 98%. Collaborated with vendors, contractors, and insured during coverage investigations to expedite the claim handling process.

## AEROSPACE PROPULSION CRAFTSMAN-STAFF SERGEANT

UNITED STATES AIR FORCE (USAF) Feb 2012 – Feb 2018

Facilitated and tracked training progression, supply chain parts, and maintenance activities, demonstrating superior diligence, time management, and supervisory skills. Implemented training plans in response to an influx of new and inexperienced employees, ensuring full qualification of 10 trainees in one year. Created web-based tracking system to monitor inspection and maintenance activities, increasing equipment serviceability rate to 98%.

Trained and adapted six new airmen to increased base security operations during hostile negotiations with the North Korean government. Supervised and certified 19 airmen on 114 aircraft and support equipment tasks, reducing maintenance backlogs by 200%. Facilitated sales for the procurement of mission-essential aircraft and support equipment through local and foreign supply chains in the Asian Pacific.